I was going to take that as an afterthought.
Are you self-producing properly?
Should I pay for it?
Hi, I'm Mr. Tokyo Day. Please.
Please.
And please give my regards to Mr. Sokoma.
Please do.
And now, here they are again today. Please come in.
Interesting, interesting, interesting. They are all funny.
If it's comedy you want, we've got it.
Leave it to us.
Ready.
Ruff Ruff.
Please do.
So, that's it. This time, we're going to do our very popular project, the series on losing a battle.
I see.
We learned a lot from Mr. Otani last time he was here, didn't we?
Do you remember?
Wearing the hat?
That's right. When you wear a hat, when you say hello, it makes you feel like you've said hello.
I think it's right.
I also wear a hat when I enter Fuji TV these days.
Oh, we passed each other at Teletext the other day, didn't we?
Teletext wasn't wearing a hat.
Teletoon doesn't wear a hat.
Teletubbies don't need to say hello.
They usually don't wear hats. They are learning a lot, aren't they?
They are learning.
We can all learn a lot in this way, and I would like to do it again this time.
This time, I would like to ask a top idol who worked in various jobs and was a multi-talented person among the top idols about how he/she performed in the first round in detail.
I see. Then, let's call him up right away. This person is here. Please come in.
Please give my regards to her.
I am Mai Niinouchi. Pleased to meet you.
Please give my regards to you.
I would like to introduce Mai Niinouchi, formerly of Nogizaka 46. Please give me a hand.
I cried because of my fast pace.
You're early.
You're early?
Too soon.
Why didn't you cry when you were looking over there?
I was about to cry, but I thought, "If I cry, who will come?
I don't know what I said in the second half. I was crying too much.
Who was your favorite?
Nanase Nishino.
Not at all. Not at all.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Sakuma mentioned earlier that Ms. Niinouchi is active in multiple fields,
You are an idol and an office worker at the same time, aren't you?
Yes, I was also an office worker at one time.
It's amazing, isn't it, being an office worker at the same time?
In parallel, she supported me so that I didn't have to come to work when I got busier and busier.
I see.
And, as he said, I became busier and busier, and my attendance gradually decreased, and finally I was able to leave the company amicably, for which I am very grateful.
That's right, Shinnai-san. There were many ups and downs, weren't there?
There were many ups and downs.
I started out as an underdog, so it was a long road before I was selected,
I was also allowed to do OL Night Nippon,
I was also allowed to do the OL Night Nippon, and I had to go up from the third round, called "Zero," to the first round.
So, Mr. Shinnai, you have something you want to tell everyone in Rough Rough.
Yes, that's right.
What is it?
Are you all self-producing?
Are you self-producing?
Oh, I'm done once more.
It's as if we've only taken out the words, "Are you all self-producing?
Self-produce?
Yes.
What does that mean exactly?
I believe that there is always a chance.
Yes, yes, yes.
But I don't think they are equal.
So, I always try to be ready for any opportunity that may come my way,
I have always thought that self-production is important,
I hope you can learn that today.
Wow, you said it so well, Mr. Shinnai.
Oh, my.
In baseball, if you are not prepared for the pitch to come, you can't take a chance, right?
If you suddenly stand up in the batter's box, you will get nervous, won't you?
So I think it is important to do it on a regular basis.
What is it that you do?
I would like to ask you that first.
I will put it to you as a question now.
Yes, I will.
So, this time, we are going to have a self-production quiz to learn from Mr. Shinnai.
Let's go to the first question.
First of all, Ms. Shinnai has been very successful in producing a certain character by herself.
What exactly is this character?
In short, did you create it when you were an underdog in Nogizaka?
Yes, I did.
I started it when All Night Nippon Zero started.
I see.
Please give us the first men's episode in a while.
Oh, you're early.
I'm early too.
No, it's too early.
You know what I mean?
I know.
You're the last one to do it.
I'm doing it last.I'm doing it last.
Yes.
Now, the character that we launched.
Yes, Saito.
I launched the office worker character.
Oh, I see.
Just because I'm an office worker.
That's not it.
That's right.
Yes, someone.
It's okay if I'm not in the room.
Everyone's hand-raising speed has slowed down.
Either you guys stopped raising your hands at once, or you don't want to be disliked, or you're coming first.
Yes, um...
What character?
What character did I push out?
The event, Saito.
I pushed out the Amego character.
Uh, a little bit.
Sure, sure.
There is a recurrent survey.
Well, but, well, well, it's different.
Now, yes, Nakamatsu.
MC Cara.
Oh.
You say, "I can do radio, too.
But still, it's not there.
That's right.
He is a bit involved with idols.
Idol-related.
I'm talking about idol-related things.
Oh, my.
Well, then, we'll know more and more about the results.
Come on, I thought you were wrong about Hayashi.
Yes.
What was it, Hayashi?
A water thief?
A water thief.
That kind of character?
A water thief character.
That's right.
When I was an office worker, I worked on the 7th floor,
There was a large floor on the 5th floor, and that was the only floor with water servers.
Yes, yes, yes.
I had to go from the 7th floor to the 5th floor unless I had something important to do,
But I only went to the 5th floor to get a water server,
So I told him that the kid on the 7th floor was stealing water from the server,
So I said, "He's a water thief, isn't he?
I said, "She's a water thief, isn't she?
He said he couldn't sell that character.
A water thief.
But she was teased a bit for being a water thief on Nogizaka Kenkenchu, wasn't she?
That's right.
When I graduated, Bananaman gave me a suite,
I was able to improve my personality as well,
Yes, I graduated.
It means that I will be expected to be a mangy character.
That's not it.
It's about idols.
It's more about idols.
If only we were idols.
If only they listened to the radio.
Oh, I see.
Yui is the only fan here today.
I see.
A big fan.
Idol.
When we were thinking about what we should do if we were to do this.
Can we do it?
Are you afraid?
Okay, Hibino.
Wonder Girl Character
Wonder girl.
Ah...
Well, you know, as an idol character.
Indeed.
But it's not that.
It's like, I don't know, how should I put it...
It's not like she's an easy to understand wonder girl or anything.
It's more like, "I've got you there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You should just say it anyway.
Okazaki
A character that saves money
Oh, there was that too
I was a contract character
Oh, I see.
Contract contract contract
I had that, too.
That's not the point.
Yes, Fujisaki
Library character.
Bookstore?
Like the library.
Like he's solid.
Like Byoin is like this.
That's why you liked Gita, right?
You have a favorite...
I don't know what to say, but...
Yes...Yes, sir.
Second guess character.
Oh, that's correct.
Excellent.
Oh.
That's correct.
That's your second guess.
Yes, I'm working on a two guess character.
What does this mean?
Well, I was doing the radio show with the idea that I'm not the first choice.
I've been doing the radio show with the idea that I'm not the first guessed character, but the second guessed character.
But when you say that...
But when I say that, I mean that popular members who are my first favorite
they can't get the right to shake hands with you, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
So, if you give me your second favorite, I'll give you the right to shake hands with me.
I'll get the handshake for the ones I didn't get.
Oh!
I'm going to take all the people who say they're the second best guess.
I'm going to take all of them.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, so you already got them.
I'm going to use it as a receptacle.
And, besides...
Did I say so clearly about the popularity itself?
No, I didn't. I don't know.
But there are many good points.
I mean, I can be the recipient of people who are pushing for the popular members.
I go to the handshake meeting every night.
I go to the handshake every night.
I get a little nervous.
I'm a little nervous, so I'm here to break in.
You're just trying to get used to it?
You don't feel sad to hear that, do you?
Not at all. You're the second person to ask me for a handshake.
Isn't it better than not?
I see.
That's a positive way of thinking, isn't it?
So, Mr. Ashiogo, before Maian...
You're the one who came to the handshake event.
I'll do it.
Maian after this
So, the person who came to the handshake meeting at Shinyunchi's place
Wow, next Mai-an.
I'm just getting used to my shoulders.
Hello.
I'm looking forward to meeting you.
We'll be at Mai-Yuan later.
Maian after this? I'm so nervous.
I'm nervous, but I'm used to it.
Oh, really? Good. Have a good day.
Have a good day.
Oh, that's nice.
I don't know about that.
It's warm and inviting.
But I thought...
He held my hand the whole time, like it was a push.
Oh, there's a difference
It's just you
It's a difference
But if you say it's one drop that much
On the contrary, what do you say
I have a thing for someone I admire, but...
Like you're going to like your childhood friend.
That kind of thing.
So there were people who changed from 2 to 1?
Of course there are.
And the ones who are willing to give you a push...
They're always declaring that they're my number one choice.
Like, "I'm your number one choice," or "I'm your number one favorite.
Like, "I'm the top favorite.
It makes the bond stronger.
She's an all-nighter.
You said she's the second-best girl.
That's right. He said she's his second choice.
I said, "The woman of the second push is doing the Raj.
I was preparing myself.
No, that's good.
Thank you very much.
Now, then.
Mr. Paction Problem...
Hiroyama Kanda, Teruyuki Tsuchida...
Mr. New Universe, who also performs with his super seniors.
In order to win the hearts of the seniors
What is the habit he has acquired to win the hearts of his seniors?
And what is this?
What is this?
To win the hearts of the seniors.
You've been working with the bigwigs on the show, right?
That's right.
Since I was a little kid.
I've been working with people I've seen on TV since I was a little kid.
It's very nerve-wracking, isn't it?
That's why I've been so careful
I've been very careful.
This is quite understandable.
When we talk with our seniors...
But it's okay.
How should I do it?
Yes, Natsume.
I'll look up at you a little.look up a little
Bukkari-like
Mr. New Cosmos looks up at the paction problem.
You can't do that on TV, can you?
Yes, Sasaki
smiles innocently
No, but that's not what I meant.
That's not what I meant.
Yes, Saito.
To be able to talk openly
I look at the weather forecast every time
And talk about the weather.
Do you have a story in mind?
I'll make it up.
No, I don't mean that.
It's about the other person, isn't it?
Yes, Yoshimura.
You laugh so hard no matter what I talk about.
Ah...
But, well, well, well...
The nuance is a bit close, isn't it?
It's close.
It's in that vein.
Yes, Fujisaki.
When you give an aizuchi...
"As expected"...
You say something like that, don't you?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
That's what I'm trying to teach you.
That's not it.
But...
It's close.
Close, a little close.
Yes, Yoshimura.
I'll have a look at his Wiki page.
Oh, well, well, well
Well, you did that, didn't you? That's normal.
Yes, I did
Yes, Fujisaki
You say something like "I can't do that kind of thing".
Ah.
Well, you're almost right.
Excellent, yes.
It's a nuance.
You know, expose your envy.
Yes, I think it's very difficult to give a compliment.
I think it's very difficult to give a compliment, and I think it feels fake.
Especially for senpai.
That's right.
So, in the conversation
I look for something I envy.
For example, if it's Mr. Tsuchida...
Well, you have a lot of children.
I mean, four siblings sounds like a very lively family.
I envy you.
I was an only child.
That's how I would start.
Then I'll say.
Who wants to give it a try? Yoshimura
We're meeting for the first time today.
Good morning.
Nice to meet you.
Akita-san, I believe you're the bitch cabra.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Okayama Prefecture's traditional performing arts.
You've been doing that since you were little.
Yes, I've been doing it since I was about 2 years old.
Hmmm...
I've been doing it since I was a little girl.
I think it's especially good.
I think it's especially nice.
ader.
Oh no.
Well, how about you, Yu?
Is it me? I'm from Okayama,
I'm from Okayama, but I live near Saitama and suburbs,
I envy you having a family home to go back to.
Hey, you are a genius.
This tempura can be made in Ibaraki, too.
You can go anywhere.
The way he is talking is so natural,
You can hear what he's saying as if he's really thinking it.
Amazing.
Okay, I am General Saito.
Good morning.
Which part of the muscle is the best?
What part of the muscle?
My muscles, where I can show off my muscles?
My back?
Can I ask you to try the best pose?
It's the best.
Why do you give us a subject like this?
You can ask your senpai, right?
You can say that to your senpai.
What's your favorite pose so far?
I'm a competitive photographer, I'm a winner.
I want you to pose like this, with your eyes.
With your eyes.With your eyes.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Go home.
I was working with Bakusho Mondai.
Oda-san and I are the best at the opposite.
That's the same as saying, "You're the one who's the best at the opposite.
Yes, really.
The last part of the lesson was a practical lesson.
I see.
I think reactions are very important.
You mean the art of reaction.
I mean the art of reaction. When you are on a TV program, if you have a good reaction, the camera operator will probably think, "Oh, let's film this girl right now.
I think the camera operator will think, "Oh, let's take a picture of this girl right now.
So I think it's a good idea to improve your reaction skills.
Isn't it best not to be half-hearted?
Yes. Half-heartedness is the worst.
I think it's important to keep it natural.
I see. It's true that if you do it as an act, it will be obvious.
That's right.
Now then, let's have you ruffians try your hand at a reaction trick.
I would like to challenge you all to perform a reaction trick.
The reaction challenge will be...
The classic variety show "Gucha Gacha"!
What? That's great!
That's right, you're going to drink a very hot gacha now.
The rule is that you will be divided into 4 groups of 4 in the front row and 4 in the back row, and you will drink a very hot gacha.
But only one of them is really drinking.
And we're going to ask you to guess who that one person is.
See if you can fool Mr. Shinnai with your natural reactions.
I'll explain the plan one more time.
I'll explain the plan one more time, and we'll try Katsumina's reaction one more time.
I see.
It's a little thin now, isn't it?
Her reaction when she said "It's a very boiled gacha" was a bit thin, wasn't it?
That's why I'd like to challenge you all to a game of reaction.
Reaction game?
It's a little difficult to play.
Let's try it once.
Let's try it once with that take 2.
I'm going to ask you to react to a variety of the classic "hotchpotch" gumbo.
No way.
Hey.
You did it once.
You're so bad at this.
Next time...
Next time.
Next time
Shin-san, when you do variety shows like this, who was great at Nogizaka?
Ikuta Erika.
I can do both.
She can be extremely bitter, and she can also make you almost cry during an explosion surprise,
Because I have a lot of sensitivity, I am good at expressing it.
So you are good at expressing the number of emotions in a single line.
That's right.
When you were first in Nogizaka, were you not used to variety at all?
I heard that they were not used to it, but they were still nervous.
Well, everyone, please have a drink. Please drink.
Bon appétit.
Oh, but does it hurt?
Oh, no.
Oh, great.
You're too quiet, even for this type.
You should talk more, more, more. Even this.
The more you talk, the better.
Oh, it's bitter.
Yes, sir.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yeah.
You suck at that.
I don't get it.
I'm sure it's right here. I don't understand it when it's like this.
You're going to tear it apart.
Oh, shit.
It burns.
If it doesn't go in the mouth at all...
If there's someone with a mouth that can take it.
Okay, one at a time. One at a time.
Lin.
Poof! Breath!
Well, if you work hard, you can do it.
You can do it?
Okay, Hibino.
I'll take it.
It's okay.
Yoshimura?Yoshimura?
Yes, last Saito.
I'm fine.
Yes, sir.
It's hard.
Are you guys doing diving?
When you come out
It's all right.
You're diving, right?
Well then, Shinji-san...
The correct answer is...
What?
Hayashi!
Mr. Hayashi! Why?
I felt a little lost when I drank.
There you go. It was coming out a little.
Yes.
Then, who drank the bitter tea?
I did!
Wow!
I couldn't swallow it, and the moment I put it in my mouth, I felt something very bitter, like a cold medicine.
If I stopped here, I couldn't speak anymore.
But this was not your class, was it?
That's right!
I would probably stand and look for water or something.
If you didn't do that, you wouldn't have been taken because there were too many people?
No, they didn't. They didn't take it.
I thought that even if I was drinking in a normal, ordinary way, the camera would be taken away by someone with a big reaction or someone who is good at what they do.
Is it the same with Kazumi Nakayama?
Yes!
From the moment I held it, I was like, "Oh, my God! I've never had this before! I've never done this before!
So you have made up your own dance moves.
How bitter is it? I'm not sure if it's okay? and then he says, "Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I say no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I think we're all bitter now.
Regular tea is bitter.
We're going to record it with all the Nogizaka girls, right?
Yes, sir.
Do you have a "review session" or something like that?
But it's not a reflection session. At the end of the recording.
Everyone was like, "Maybe I should have done something better at that time.
I see.
Did you ever cry at the end of a recording session?
Yes, I have.
What about it?
Well, I couldn't say it well, or couldn't give a good answer,
I think variety is all about communication.
When that didn't go well, I felt like I made Bananaman-san feel uncomfortable,
I cried a lot.
When Bananaman is concerned about you, you become a little concerned, don't you think?
That's right.
Shall we go now?
Okay, let's go.
Gekijin catcher, please!
Bon appétit.
Oh!
Mmm!
Mnh!
Yummy!
Ha-ha-ha!
Hyah!
Here it is.
Oh, there's this place?
Natsume is too unique!
Indeed!
It's an allure!
Too much Aleu! It's okay though!
It's good. Is this true or are you practicing what you were taught?
This is still good though.
I'm not good at this.
Which is this?
Okay, Chuu-san.
Eh!
This is difficult.
Bash Nagamatsu-san Nagamatsu... I felt like the way he said he really didn't like it came out in his ears.
If it were acting, it would be great if the ears were falling.
Nagamatsu... he was so good!
He was so naive. He was trying to match himself to Sasaki's level. Because he knew Sasaki was drinking.
And Natsumi was so unique that I could easily eliminate her as the first choice.
How was this?
But it's better to move on from whatever's on your mind, especially at home.
The staff member who was working with me during the performance used to tell me that I should go into the recording as if this was my home, a place where I could make mistakes.
So I'm pretty confident that everything I do will be picked up by Bananaman and the members will follow up on it.
I'm going to try it at home because I can make mistakes at home.
I'm trying to hone my skills. I was wondering if I should pay for it.
I mean, I paid to see you, and I was so close I could only see you through binoculars, and I thought, "What am I going to do now that I'm this close to you?
I just thought Hayashi's angle was a little different. I'll give it a shot.
Are you sure? Are you sure?
Hello. Thank you. Nice to meet you.
Is Mr. Nokuso here? It's a waste, it's a waste, it's a waste.
You're a real piece of work!
Do what you've learned!
Hello, Yui Takanashi. I'm Mai Niinai.
I will do my best so that we can work together next time, please.
I hope you recover from the fever soon.
Take care. See you soon.
You there who finished watching the video!You there who finished watching the video!
You watched it all the way through! That's great!
What do you think? Did you enjoy it?
Wait a minute, didn't you subscribe to our channel?
I can't believe it!
Hit the subscribe button, and I'll give you a second to subscribe!
Come on, Monomin!
You'll want to subscribe!
Let's get hypnotized!
Thank you, you hit the subscribe button. Thank you for subscribing.